<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article>
    <continuationNote>(Continued From Page One)</continuationNote>
    <mainContent>
        <paragraph>includes 10 children, the oldest 18, the youngest, one. "And believe me they are a great joy," declares their father frequently.</paragraph>
        <section>
            <title>Built on Rock</title>
            <paragraph>He remembers with greater charity than scorn the anxiety of persons who feared he might not be able to support so large a family. "I was always a firm believer that if God intended you would have a large family, surely He would be provided for."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>"But the parents must do their part," he added. "God helps those who help themselves. The main idea is to trust in the Lord. Just live the way He expects you to live."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Two weeks before the stock market crash of October, 1929, Edmund Muenchen married Miss Hilda Lense, of Newport, Ky. By the time the market had reached its 1932 low point, they had two children. The third year twins arrived. "Sure, we had to struggle. But we worked hard and took our troubles to God."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>The first child, Mary, now 18, is a graduate of St. Xavier's commercial high school. She works as a secretary, and when St. Elizabeth's parish, Norwood, stages a play Mary is occasionally called upon to act as master of ceremonies. "I must admit I throw my chest out when I see her on the stage," her father confesses.</paragraph>
        </section>
    </mainContent>
    <sideContent>
        <paragraph>The other children are Joanne, 16, a student at St. Xavier commercial; Robert and Donald, 15-year-old twins, both freshmen at Purcell high school; William, 13, who will be graduated this year from St. Elizabeth's school; John, 11; Virginia, 9; Lawrence, 7; and John, 5, all students at St. Elizabeth's; and Paul, age one.</paragraph>
        <section>
            <title>Let's See Now</title>
            <paragraph>Muenchen ticks off his children on his fingers confidently until he comes to Sue. "I used to have them memorized," he grins, "then I got mixed up in the middle." Then he smiles his wife's "diary."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>"Hilda has all the dates written down in a book," he explains. "It would be helpful when we take the census."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Children of a large family enjoy certain advantages, according to Muenchen, who ought to know. "Our children have been taught responsibility from an early age in the most natural way possible. They know they must help each other. The little ones and the older ones especially look out for the younger children."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>One results of this is "there is much less danger of selfishness, or a child being spoiled."</paragraph>
            <paragraph>When Muenchen took his family to the WCKY studio last summer for a radio broadcast, the announcer told him it was hard to believe there were 10 children in the room. "That is because they have always been taught to be orderly and considerate," declares their father.</paragraph>
        </section>
    </sideContent>
</article>