<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article>
    <heading>Catholic Portrait</heading>
    <subheading>Furniture Salesman Finds Fame With Family of Ten</subheading>
    <author>By JAMES M. SHEA</author>
    <mainContent>
        <paragraph>Edmund F. Muenchen, Cincinnati furniture salesman, parish Holy Name officer, fraternal and civic club member, occasional bowler, devoted husband and father, awoke one morning last year and found himself famous.</paragraph>
        <paragraph>With his wife, Hilda, he received the accolade of Xavier university and parish pride when he was designated head of the "American Family of the Year from Metropolitan Cincinnati."</paragraph>
        <paragraph>Last week, when he completed plans for this year's conference (May 12-16) and for the selection of another family of the year, Edmund Muenchen still found the events of a year ago hard to credit.</paragraph>
        <paragraph>"The award was a very great honor," he said at his home. "And the way it came about was a great surprise, too. We were there when we began receiving letters from all over the country complimenting us on our wonderful family."</paragraph>
    </mainContent>
    <sidebar>
        <title>Dayton University Will Graduate 178 At June 5 Rites</title>
        <content>
            <paragraph>The University of Dayton will graduate 178 seniors and confer master's degrees on seven at commencement exercises Saturday, June 5, at 2:30 p.m. in the National Cash Register Co. auditorium.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Father George J. Renneker, S.M., president of the university, will confer the degrees.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Monsignor Frederick G. Hochwalt, a native Daytonian, who is director of the department of education of the National Catholic Welfare Conference and secretary general of the National Catholic Educational Association, will deliver the commencement address.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Monsignor Hochwalt obtained his elementary education in Holy Trinity parochial school here, and his secondary education was awarded him his A. B. degree in 1931. He holds Master's and Doctor's degrees from the Catholic University of America. Since December, 1944, Monsignor Hochwalt has been director of the Commission on American Citizenship of the Catholic University of America.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>Baccalaureate services will be held in the Immaculate Conception chapel on the University campus, Sunday, May 30, with a High Mass celebrated at 10 a.m. by Father Charles Collins, vice president and dean of the university. Father Collins will also preach the baccalaureate sermon.</paragraph>
        </content>
    </sidebar>
    <image>
        <caption>Edmund F. Muenchen</caption>
        <subcaption>Trust in the Lord</subcaption>
    </image>
    <pagination>
        <reference>Turn to Page 3 — Column 4</reference>
    </pagination>
</article>